{
   "Sports":{
      "easy":[
         {
            "questionText":"Which sport awards the Ryder's Cup?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Hockey",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Football",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Baseball",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Golf",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":3
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Which American Football player had the nickname 'Sweetness'?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Damon Allen",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Walter Payton",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Earl Campbell",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Tom Brady",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":1
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Who won the 2013 National Basketball Association (NBA) title?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Miami Heat",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"LA Lakers",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Chicago Bulls",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"San Antonio Spurs",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":0
         },
         {
            "questionText":"In which city do the Steelers compete in the NFL?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Denever",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"New York",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Pittsburgh",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Seattle",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":2
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Which NHL Team are nicknamed the 'Coyotes'?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Ottowa",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Arizona",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Calgary",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Vancouver",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":1
         }
      ],
      "medium":[
         {
            "questionText":"Which sport awards the Ryder's Cup?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Hockey",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Football",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Baseball",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Golf",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":3
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Which American Football player had the nickname 'Sweetness'?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Damon Allen",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Walter Payton",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Earl Campbell",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Tom Brady",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":1
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Who won the 2013 National Basketball Association (NBA) title?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Miami Heat",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"LA Lakers",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Chicago Bulls",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"San Antonio Spurs",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":0
         },
         {
            "questionText":"In which city do the Steelers compete in the NFL?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Denever",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"New York",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Pittsburgh",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Seattle",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":2
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Which NHL Team are nicknamed the 'Coyotes'?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Ottowa",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Arizona",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Calgary",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Vancouver",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":1
         }
      ],
      "difficult":[
         {
            "questionText":"Which sport awards the Ryder's Cup?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Hockey",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Football",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Baseball",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Golf",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":3
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Which American Football player had the nickname 'Sweetness'?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Damon Allen",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Walter Payton",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Earl Campbell",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Tom Brady",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":1
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Who won the 2013 National Basketball Association (NBA) title?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Miami Heat",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"LA Lakers",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Chicago Bulls",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"San Antonio Spurs",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":0
         },
         {
            "questionText":"In which city do the Steelers compete in the NFL?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Denever",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"New York",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Pittsburgh",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Seattle",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":2
         },
         {
            "questionText":"Which NHL Team are nicknamed the 'Coyotes'?",
            "answers":[
               {
                  "text":"Ottowa",
                  "gesture":"fist"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Arizona",
                  "gesture":"fingers_spread"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Calgary",
                  "gesture":"wave_in"
               },
               {
                  "text":"Vancouver",
                  "gesture":"wave_out"
               }
            ],
            "correctIndex":1
         }
      ]
   }
}